我最讨厌恐怖片
l hate scary movies
我得K书，我要交生物作业
l should be studying You know l got a bio due
我不是说过 票是免费的吗？
Baby, did l mention these tickets are free?
免费的
Free
珊卓布拉克的电影也在上映
Sandra Bullock is playing right down the street
没人要花250元看布拉克
Nobody will pay seven fifty to see some Sandra Bullock shit
除非她裸体
Unless she is naked
你却会想看没大牌的
But you will sit through a movie called ''Stab''?
“失声尖叫” 刺激肾上腺素
Adrenaline, Maureen
惊吓可刺激起人类本能
lt is good to be scared. lt is primal. You know what l'm saying
我来告诉你这是什么电影
No, l'm gonna tell you what it is. Okay?
就是无聊白人女孩被追杀
lt's a dumb ass white movie about some dumb ass white girls・ ・ ・
一部无聊的白人被追杀的电影
getting their white asses cut the fuck up, okay?
你以为珊卓布拉克是黑人啊？
Yeah, and l suppose Sandra Bullock is miss ethnicity? Right?
恐怖片向来排斥黑人
No, l'm saying that the horror genre is historical for excluding ・ ・ ・
the African-American element
你几时拿到黑人电影博士学位
When did you get your PHD in black cinema, sister soldier?
我有看“娱乐周刊” 我知道
Listen, l read my ''Entertainment Weekly'', l know my shit
我也看“黑人电影圈”
Yeah, Maureen, l read my ''Black Beat'' too, homey
你要全黑的电影？ 黑人卡司
Are you going to have a all-black movie?Black-cast? All-black wardrobe
黑眼珠？黑猫？
Black-eyes peas? Black cats?
嘿，拿着
Hi, here you go・ ・ ・
这是什么？
What's this?
纪念品，片厂送的
''Stab'' souvenirs, studio sent them
白色的耶，谢谢
And it's white, thanks
真有够浪漫
Very romantic
改编自魏盖儿原著 “伍兹镇谋杀案”
她干嘛非得裸体？
So, why does she got to be naked? What does that have to do・ ・ ・
她光溜溜的 关剧情什么事
with the plot of the story her being butt-ass naked
那我倒不知道，我勃起了
Well, l don't know about the plot but l have got a stiffy
自己打手枪吧
You better loosen up that wrist
喂
Hello?
Hello
哪位？
Who is this?
你猜
Guess
不，真的，哪位？
No, really, who is this?
你在等人吗？
Were you expecting somebody?
没有
No
蠢货，挂他电话
Bitch, hang the phone up and ''star-69'' his ass!
哪一位？
Who is this?
你希望是谁？
Who would you like it to be?
我不喜欢玩游戏，哪位？
l don't like games. Who is this?
看后面，看到你男朋友没？
Look out back Do you see your boyfriend anywhere?
我现在没男朋友
l don't even have a boyfriend right now
想要一个吗？
Would you like one?
给我钱，我要买爆米花
Give me some money l need to get some popcorn
你自己有钱
You got money
那是我的钱，我要你的钱
l got ''my'' money l asked for your money
你说好不好？
What do you say?
快啊，怎么不说话
Come on. Cat got your tongue?
我还不认识你 就不喜欢你了
You know, l don't even know you and l dislike you already
嘿，卖光了
Hey, we're sold out
中的爆米花 一杯小健怡可乐
Hi. Can l have a medium popcorn no butter. And a small diet Pepsi
好的
You got it
够了，我不回里面去
That's it l am not going back in there
胆小鬼，只是电影嘛
Come on, you chicken shit it's just a movie
这不只是电影 这是真实故事
Not it's not just a movie lt's a true story
这些人几年前 在加州被杀
All these kids got killed a couple of years ago in California
好讨厌
You ass!
对不起，我只想吓你
l'm sorry, l had to, baby
你干嘛要吓我
Why are you playing?
别紧张
Would you relax?
我不喜欢被吓 我不喜欢
l don't like being scared l don't like that
宝贝，只是电影嘛
Baby, it's just a movie
而且恐怖片 是很棒的前戏
Besides scary movies are great foreplay
拜托！
Excuse me?
我们去看珊卓布拉克好了
Let's go see Sandra Bullock
不，都开演了，留下吧
No, Sandra's started already We can stay
你别这么爱闹就好了
Just stop playing so much
好，我要上厕所
Alright l have to go to the bathroom
里面见
See you inside
对不起
Sorry
有人吗？
Hello?
不…别那么做
No, no! Don't do that
快，快，走啊
Move, move・ ・ ・ Go
宝贝，别闹了
Baby, give it up
回来得正好，她快被杀了
You came back just in time, it looks like she's just about to get it
要爆米花吗？
Want some popcorn?
换成是我，我会离开那边
lf that was me, l'd be out of there
来了
Here it comes
惊声尖叫2
喂
Hello
喂，席妮
Hello, Sidney
哪位？
Who this is?
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
What's your favorite scary movie?
哪位？
Who is this?
你告诉我啊
You tell me
科瑞吉利斯，5550176
Cory Gillis, 55501 7 6
妈的
Shit
别气馁，科瑞
hot flash, Cory
你可以找刑事检察官
Call criminal offense prosecutor on the penal code 653M
希望你喜欢“失声尖叫”
Hope you enjoy the movie
又要换号码了？
Time to change numbers again
会熬过去的，周末才上映呢
No, it will die off. lt's opening weekend. Let's see how it goes
好
Okay
你知道，朗
You know, Ron
被冤枉犯罪一定不好受
lt's not an easy thing to be accused of a crime you didn't commit
尤其是谋杀 这么恐怖的罪
Particularly one as heinous as murder
真相大白后 大家怎么对待你
But how do people treat you now that they know the truth about your innocence
大半人都不错
Most people are good
有些人还是保持距离
There are still some that keep a safe distance
我觉得很奇怪 毕竟我一向是个平凡人
which is odd for me 'cause l've always been sort of a people person
你被冤枉 现已宣判无罪
You were wrongly accused You were fully exonerated
曾经被判有罪的人
That and a nickel gets you a cup of coffee
要完全洗刷清白 不太容易
Even that's not true anymore
魏盖儿的书，还有电影
Certainly with Gale Weather's book and now the movie・ ・ ・
洗刷了卡顿维瑞的冤情
it sets the record straight for Cotton Weary
大家可能会觉得 魏盖儿够意思
One would think Gale has been terrific through all this・ ・ ・
快点，要迟到了
Hey! Move your ass, you're late
别忘了固定的聚会
And don't forget about the routine mixer and the Delta Lambda Zeta
我看我去不了了
l don't think l'll be able to make it, Hal
什么？ 别想翘头，你答应过
What! Don't even try to bag you promised me
随便答应而已
A vague promise at best
这是免费啤酒 交朋友的派对
Nobody's asking you to join. lt's a party. Free beer, meet the girls
你知道我不太喜欢 宗教聚会
Hallie, you know me and organized religion
这是姐妹会
lt's a sorority・ ・ ・
那更糟
Worse
你不要太孤僻
Look Sid, lower the walls for the next few days
孤立自己不太好
This self-induced isolation you got going is not healthy
我没事
l'm fine
是，我知道
l'm fine. Yeah, l know
说没事却绷着个脸
l'm fine is stretched tightly across your face
赶快看新闻
Check out the news
两名温莎学院的学生
The two Windsor college students were murdered last night・ ・ ・
昨晚看“失声尖叫”时遇害
during a sneak preview of the new movie, ''Stab''
警方目前只公布被害人姓名
Police have not released any infor- mation except for the victims names
但今晚稍后将举行记者会
But a press conference has been scheduled later today
两名被害人皆为大四学生
The victims, Maureen Evens & Phil Stevens were both Windsor seniors
蓝迪在哪儿？
Where's Randy?
他早上有电影理论课
He's got film theory this morning
席妮
Sidney
你认识被害人吗？
Did you know the victims?
这些命案对你造成威胁吗？
Did you feel threatened by the murders?
你想会发生更多命案吗？
Do you think they'll be more murders?
告诉我们有关被害人的事
What can you tell us about the victims, Sid?
发表一点意见好吗？
We just need one statement
电影剧情造成 戏院谋杀事件
You could say what happened in that theater is a direct result of the movie itself
这样子的说法太假道学了
That is so moral majority
现实生活的暴力不能怪娱乐
You can't blame real life violence on entertainment
当然可以，你不看新闻吗？
Yes, you can Don't you even watch the news?
拜托，凶手戴电影的鬼面具
Hello? The murderer was wearing a Ghost mask
不怪电影怪谁
Just like in the movie lt's directly responsible
电影不该为我们的行为负责
No, it's not. Movies are not responsible for our actions
但电影是模仿现实的伟大艺术
lt's a classic case of life imitating art, imitating life
凶杀案不该模仿，更不是艺术
This is not a hypothetical lt's not about that
死者是我的同学 这是现实世界
l had biology with that girl This is reality
谢谢，我同意
Thank you, l agree with you
我告诉你们什么是现实
Let me tell you about reality Mickey
我亲身经历过，好吗？
l lived through this, okay?
现实生活是不能被模仿
Life is life lt doesn't imitate anything
少来了，蓝迪
Come on, Randy. With all due respect the killer obviously pattered ・ ・ ・
凶手显然在仿效 杀人狂角色
himself, after two serial killers who have been immortalized on film
谢谢
Thank you
你是说有人想演出续集？
Are you suggesting that someone is trying to make a real life sequel?
谁想那么做？续集都很烂
Stab 2? Who would wanna do that Sequel's suck
就字意看，续集就是二等的
Oh, please, please. By definition alone, they're inferior films
胡扯，很多续集成绩超越原片
Bullshit generalization. Many sequels have surpassed their originals
举例一部
Oh yeah? Name one
异形续集就比第一集好很多
''Aliens'' Far better than the first
是啊，你品味真有够差
Yeah there's no accounting for taste
谢谢，再举一部
Thank you. Ridley Scott rules Name another
异形是经典电影
Aliens is a classic, okay
“离她远点，贱货”
''Get away from her, you Bitch''
拜托，正确台词是 “别靠近她，贱货”
l believe the line is ''Stay away from her, you Bitch''This is film class right?
好，随便，你懂我意思
Whatever, you know what l mean
魔鬼终结者2
Another・ ・ ・T-2
你很爱卡麦隆，是不是
You got a hard on for Cameron
爱疯了
A big one
第一集已是老掉牙的历史
Wait a second the first Terminator is historical
莎拉康纳
''Sarah Conner'' ''Yes''
好，好，“恐怖屋续集”
Alright, alright ''House 2'' the second story
所有的恐怖片都被续集破坏了
The entire horror genre was destroyed by sequels
有了，有了
l got it by the way, l got it
教父II
The Godfather Part 2
很好，获得金像奖的例外
That's very good An Oscar Winning Exception
好，够了，今天到此为止
Alright, that's enough That will be a wrap
下次再继续探讨续集
The sequel discussion to be continued
创意先生，你如何使续集成功
So, Mister Originality how would you make it different
要让结局大爆冷门
l would let the geek get the girl
三百个人在戏院里，没人去救
Three hundred people watching and nobody did anything
他们以为是宣传，天哪
They thought it was a publicity stunt. For Christ's sake
如果是宣传 这点子可精彩极了
And it would have been a good one too
蓝迪，事情又开始了
lt's starting again, Randy
不，看电影才会碰到倒霉事
lt's not Shit happens at the movies
被抢、变残废、被谋杀
People get robbed, shot maimed, murdered
影城现在是很危险的地方
The multiplex is just very dangerous place be these days
你不要每件事都否定它
You're in extreme denial
你也该这样 这跟我们无关
And you should be too This has nothing to do with us
戴面具的人在戏院
Randy. A guy in a Ghost mask hacked up two people・ ・ ・
砍了两个人
in a movie theater telling our life stories
只是巧合
Coincidence
你不能当做没事发生
You know what happened in Woodsboro Randy. You can't ignore it
我知道 我不再重蹈覆辙
l know Sid. l don't wanna go back there again
我们不能假装快乐的生活吗
Can't we just go back to our pseudo-quasi happy existence?
德瑞克，你好
Hello Derek, how you doing?
席妮，我到处找你
Sid, l've been looking everywhere
我听说了，你没去上课
l heard, you weren't in class
我受不了“众所瞩目”的感觉
Yeah, l know. l couldn't take all the ''that's her'' looks
有什么我能做的？
ls there anything l can do?
教我如何假装快乐的生活
You have any tricks to take us back to a pseudo-quasi happy existence?
有个办法
You know l just might have one for that
是吗？是什么？
Oh yeah, what is it?
这满不错的
That was pretty good
去开房间啦
Get a room
他们威胁要怎样？ 别开玩笑
They're threatening what? Are you kidding me?
让电影下片太蠢了
lt would be stupid to pull this movie
免费宣传 这个周末会大卖
All this free press, they're going to have huge numbers this weekend
它会打破卖座记录
lt'll break box office records
没问题
Consider it done
魏小姐，嗨，我是乔
Miss Weathers! Hi. l'm Joel the affiliate sent me
新来的摄影师
l'm the new cameraman
有经验吗？
You got experience?
我拍过宾果总决赛 差点得奖
Yeah, l'm local but l shot the Bingo Finals. Almost got an award for that
好，我告诉你怎么做
Alright. Listen Joel this is how it works
我指示你就拍
l point, you shoot
要专注，动作要快
You stay focused and fast on your feet. And we'll get along fine
你现在是专业摄影师
You're playing with the big boys now. You got it?
知道了，没问题
Got it. Got you covered. l'm all over it. Don't worry・ ・ ・
安啦，能有多难嘛 你指我拍
about a thing. How hard can it be? You point & l shoot. l'm there
对不起，魏小姐 打搅一分种
Excuse me, Miss Weathers? Could l have a minute
不喔，只要一秒种
No・ ・ ・ Just one second?
我知道你常碰到这种事
l know you probably get this all the time
我是你的忠实书迷
But l just wanted to say that l'm such a big fan of your work
我刚看完你的书，爱不释手
l just finished your book. l couldn't put it down. lnsightful, probing
我爱死你的书了
l just really really loved your book
谢谢
Thank you
我帮本地的报纸写东西
l'm a writer myself. l write for the local paper for The Post Telegraph
黛比索特
Debbie Salt
我去年参加过 你的研讨会
l took your seminar in Chicago last year
我坐在前排一直发问
l was the one in the front row asking all the questions
难怪你很面熟
l thought you looked familiar
谢谢，我迫不及待想看到电影
Thank you Can't wait to see the movie
你一定受到很多指责
You know, you must be getting quite a lot of flak on that. Right?
你怎么看暴力与电影的关系
W/ all the violence & cinema issues What is your position going to be?
不予置评
No comment
我很希望能引述你说的话
lt would be such an honor for me lf l could just get a quote from you for my story
好，开始引述
Alright, begin quote
你的马屁拍得太明显了
Your flattering remarks are both desperate and obvious. End quote
你想这些命案有关连吗？
What are you doing here? Do you think these murders are connected?
你对命案有什么看法？
What's your theory on these murders? What's your feeling on this?
对不起
Can l have your attention
我是哈利警长
My name if Chief Louis Hartley
哈利警长
Chief Hartley
魏盖儿，伍兹镇血案的作者
Hi, Gale Weathers author of the Woodsboro Murders
你想凶手会再犯案吗？
Do you think the killer will strike again?
没证据显示 这是个连续杀人狂
We have no evidence that this is a serial killer
我想读一篇…
l'd like to read from a・ ・ ・
请问你们有任何 预防措施吗？
Can you tell us of any precautions that you are taking?
我们认为这是独立的案件
First of all, we think it's just an isolated incident
我们会留意很多可能性
And we will be caring out many possibilities
我的天，事情大条了
Oh my God, this is huge
有嫌犯了吗？
Do you have any suspects?
席妮，你看，魏盖儿
Sidney, look, it's Gale Weathers
什么？
What?
魏盖儿的记者会
starring in the Gale Weathers Press Conference
魏盖儿的书
based on the book by Gale Weathers
她将主演魏盖儿的电影
Soon to be a major motion picture starring Gale Weathers
别太毒了 她救过我们
Be kind, she saved our lives
她脑袋秀逗了
She had calf-implants
你打算实施宵禁吗？
Chief Hartley, do you have plan on giving the town a curfew?
我要去听她说什么
l'm gonna get closer
她就是魏盖儿？
So that's her?
对
Yeah
女孩们，你们还好吧？
Hello girls, enjoying yourselves?
洛伊斯姐妹，墨菲姐妹
Hello, Sister Lois Sister Murphy
嗨，席妮
Hi, Sidney
感觉很可怕吧？ 撑得住吗？
This must be flat out hell for you How are you holding up?
我尽量
l manage
真奇怪，为了你 搞得鸡飞狗跳
lt's weird, isn't it? To think this fuss is all because of you
真是基努李维的连锁反应
l mean not directly. But in some six degrees of Kevin Bacon way
海莉，你会带你朋友 来聚会吧
Are you going to bring your friend to our little martini mixer tonight?
我有很多功课…
l have a lot of work to・ ・ ・
我们会到
We'll be there
很好，我们会看着你的
Good, Because Sid we have our eyes on you
坚强点，入会后 就是一家人了
You hang in there, and if there is anything we can do the Delta Lambdas are very sensitive to your plight
对，再见
Yeah ・ ・ ・Bye
你入会后要穿成那样吗？
You going to start to dress like that when you get in?
杀了我吧！
That's not going to happen
DL姐妹会是一群臭…
The Delta Lambdas are the biggest bunch of fucking ・ ・ ・
我要入会，谢谢你哦
l'm pledging Delta Lambda thank you
我的天
Oh my God
那是谁？
Who's that?
杜威
Dewey?
你在这儿做什么？
What are you doing here?
我很担心你
l was worried about you
事情一发生我就搭机赶来
l heard about what happened l was on the next plane
可以谈谈吗？
Can we talk?
好啊
Yeah, yeah
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我很好
l'm fine, Dewey
事情发生前都很好
Or was・ ・ ・ Things were okay Until now
不过我主演的戏 两天后公演
The theater's going great. l got my first starring role,open in two days
太棒了
That is great
对，我很高兴还有很多好朋友
Yeah, l'm loving it And l've got some great friends
我交了个男朋友
And l'm seeing someone
他念医科 没精神错乱倾向
Nice guy, pre-med no apparent psychotic tendencies
我只是担心
l was just worried
如果有变态狂想学比利
Look Sid, if there is some freaked out psycho trying to follow in Billy Loomis' footsteps
你八成已经认识他…或她
You probably already know him Or her
或他们
or them
他们才不会放过你
They're probably already in your life
从你的生活中可以得到刺激
They get off on that
你要小心
l just want you to be careful, Sid.
我怎么会不清楚？
You think l don't know that
可是我能怎么办？
What am l suppose to do?
跟每个人断绝关系躲起来
Cut everybody off crawl under a rock? What?
当心点就是了
Just watch out Keep an eye out
我去跟哈利警长谈一谈
l'm going to talk to Chief Hartley and the local police
我会留下来注意你的安危
l'm going to just hang around l want to make sure you're safe
可以吗？
lf that's alright with you?
好
Yeah
没事吧
Hey, you okay?
那个人是谁？
Who was that guy?
老朋友
An old friend
伍兹镇的副警长，他来干嘛
Deputy Dewey. Woodsboro's finest What's he doing here?
他担心我 就像我们的大哥哥
He's worried Our surrogate big brother
葬礼最能让家人团聚
Nothing like a funeral to bring the family together
我去打招呼
l'm going to go say Hi
哈利警长说 那女孩被刺七刀
Chief Hartley said the girl was stabbed seven ・ ・ ・
别说了
Drop it
席妮，你好吗？
Hello, Sidney, how are you?
嗨，什么事？
Hi, what do you want, Gale?
我希望跟你谈几句话
l was hoping l might get a few words with you
卡顿
Cotton ・ ・ ・
嗨，席妮
Hi, Sidney
这里是温莎学院 在此，席妮与卡顿…
Here we are at Windsor College where Sidney Prescott has just・ ・ ・
自她曾误控他谋杀她母亲后…
be united with Cotton Weary for the first time since she wrongly・ ・ ・
首度重逢
accused him of murdering her mother
你在干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
我们想知道你的感受
We want to know how you feel?
告诉我们你这两年的情形
Tell us everything that has happened Looking back on the last two years
我想说我原谅你 也忘了过去
Sidney, l'd just like to say that l forgive and forget
和你一样我只想好好过日子
Just like you, l'd like to get back on with my own life
你有任何话要说吗？
Do you have any comments?
贱货
You bitch
席妮，请跟我们分享
Sidney, share with us please
我会跟你分享的
l'll share with you
好，好，好
Okay, okay, okay
拍下来没？
Did you get that on film?
拍下来了
Yes, l got that on film
席妮，等等 她去哪？席妮
Sid? Wait, wait where's she going, Gale? Sidney?
她去哪里？
Where's she going?
不是正式访问吗？ 怎么回事
Gale, l thought we had an official interview. What's going on?
她不知道？
She didn't know?
真冷酷
That was cold ・ ・ ・
搞清楚，我们不是来讨人喜欢的
You need to check your conscious at the door, sweetie,We're not here to be loved
你答应我十分钟的全国报导
Gale, you promised me ten minutes of national coverage
等我访问到你就有 他妈的十分钟报导
You'll get your ten minutes when l get my God damned interview
别掉头就走，我还…
Don't walk away from me, Gale l'm still ・ ・ ・
我做了我该做的部份
Gale, l did my part
乔
Joel
杜威，你怎会出现在这里？
Dewey. What are you doing here?
你为什么不放过她
Why don't you just leave her alone
她受的还不够吗？
Hasn't she been through enough?
还有，我的名字是德威
And my name is Dwight
我只是做我份内的事
l'm just doing my job, Dwight
任何人受伤都没关系吗？
No matter who gets hurt in the process
是谁又挨了一拳？
Who got punched here, again
我也不喜欢暴力 可是你活该
l don't condone violence but maybe you deserved it
在书中第32页，你写到
Page thirty-two
“笨手笨脚的杜威副警长”
Deputy Dewey filled the room with his Barney Fifish presence
你看过我的书
You read my book
我常看书，魏小姐
Yes, l do read, Miss Weathers
别生气，那只是书中人物
Dewey, don't take it so seriously lt's just a character in a book
41页，副警长很没经验
Page forty-one Deputy Dewey oozed with inexperience
你不觉得你反应过度吗？
Don't you think you're overacting just a little bit?
不，我觉得你是个贪图名利的
No, what l think is you're a money-hungry, fame-seeking ・ ・ ・
二流作家
and forgive me for saying mediocre writer
你根本没血没眼泪
who has a cold storage shed where her heart should be
别见怪
No offense intended
我不是故意的…
Dewey, l never meant to imply・ ・ ・
你怎么知道我没经验
How do you know my dimwitted inexperience isn't merely a subtle・ ・ ・
难道你是故意贬低我
form of manipulation used to lower people's expectations thereby・ ・ ・
免得观众对我期望太高？
enhancing my ability to effectively maneuver within any given situation?
对不起
l'm sorry
除了抱歉我不知道该说什么
l don't know what else to say Except, l'm sorry
我才抱歉，我看错你了
No. l'm the one that's sorry l misjudged you
失陪，我去执行 我的瘪三警察任务
Now, if you'll excuse me l have some oozing to do
还有一件事，头发染得不错
One more thing. Nice streaks
我不是强迫推销姐妹会的人
l am not a sorority pusher
我只是觉得这是个肯定人生
l just think despite its trivialities
稳定心理的健康环境
it's a life affirming, mentally stable healthy environment for you
看看这个地方
Look at this place
你心理学修得太过火了
l think you're talking your psych- major a little too seriously, Hallie
我没事
l'm fine
“我没事”变成你的口头禅了
That's beginning to become your theme song. l'm fine
没安全感，神经质，情绪化
Yeah, fucked up, lnsecure Neurotic and Emotional
席妮，你来啦
Sidney, you made it
嗨，我很认真的说，嗨
Hi. No l really mean that, Hi
要喝东西吗？
Do you girls want a drink?
我们自己来
Actually, we'll get it ourselves
他们还在一起吗？ 我三周没看了
l love those guys, are they still together?l haven't seen it in 3 weeks
没有，又分手了
No, they broke up again Sarah, found out that
莎拉发现巴利跟关儿上床 又像两集前那样把他甩了
Bailey slept with Gwen She dumped him like two episodes ago
真希望她心情好起来
l wish she'd get her shit together
等等，有人插播
Hold on, someone's calling
奥比兹宿舍
Omega Beta Zeta
喂
Hello
什么事？
Yes?
你是哪位？
Who is this?
西西，你哪位？
Cici. Who's this?
你以为呢？
Who do you think?
泰德，你在哪？ 你醉了吗？
Ted? Where are you are you drinking?
等等
Hold on
泰德好像醉了 我再打给你
Ted's on the other line He sounds drunk, l'll call you back?
他喝醉才打给你 别去找他
That shit only calls you when he's drunk. Don't go over there, Cici
好，我再打给你
Alright, alright l'll call you back
泰德，你好像醉了 怎么了？
Okay Ted, you sound loaded What's up?
谁是泰德？
Who's Ted?
对不起，我以为你是别人
l'm sorry. My bad ears l thought you were someone else
没关系，我是别人
That's okay. l am
你找谁？ 这边没人在
Who are you calling for nobody's here
大家都去哪？
Where is everybody?
我们今晚协办酸雨慈善会
We're co-sponsoring the Acid Rain Mixer at the Phi Gamma Alpha tonight
你怎么没去？
Why aren't you there?
我留守以便接送 喝醉的姐妹
l'm sober sister l have to be here in case a drunk sister calls and needs a ride
太可惜了
That's too bad
喝酒不闹事是我们的座右铭
Drink with your brain That's our motto
你打来找谁？
Who are you calling for?
如果我说你呢？
What if l said, you?
如果我说再见呢？
What if l said goodbye?
你干嘛要那么做？
Why would you wanna do that?
你干嘛老用问题 来回答问题
Why do you always answer a question with a question?
我喜欢打破沙锅问到底
l'm inquisitive
我没耐心，你要留话吗？
Yeah, and l'm impatient Do you want to leave a message・ ・ ・
你今晚想死吗？西西
Do you want to die tonight, Cici?
奥比兹宿舍
Omega Beta Zeta
是泰德吗？
So was it Teddy?
不，是个想吓人的变态狂
No, it was some creep asshole trying to scare me
都是电影招来一堆疯子
lt's the movie STAB lt's bringing out the crazies
该死
Shit
怎么了？
What is it?
我听到声音
l heard a noise
哪里？
Where?
楼上
Upstairs
该死
Shit
喂
Hello? Hello?
杀杀杀，死死死
Kill, kill, kill. Die, die, die
别闹了
Stop it
我不敢相信你一个人在
l can't believe you're alone in that house
我觉得屋子里有人
l don't think l'm alone
我要离开这边
l'm out of here
电话收讯不良，你在哪？
You're breaking up. Where are you?
外面
Outside
别慌，打给校警
Don't panic, sweetie Call Campus Security
好
Okay
校警
Campus Security
嗨，我是从…
Hi, l'm calling from
听得到了吗？
Can't hear・ ・ ・ Hello? Hello? Can you hear me now?
喂，该死
Hello? Shit
校警
Campus Security
喂，我是从…
Yes, l'm calling from ・ ・ ・
我听不到，喂
l can't hear you. Hello?
有人在骚扰我，喂
l'm calling from the Omega Beta Zeta house. Someone's harassing me
该死
Shit
天哪，你吓死我了
Jesus, Dawnie, you scared me
对不起，有人打来找我吗
l'm sorry. Did anyone call for me?
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
我住这儿，记得吗？
l live here, remember?
我以为你去聚会了
l just thought you were going to the mixer
我得换衣服，我要走了
Yeah, l had to change So l'll be out of here now
奥比兹宿舍
Omega Beta Zeta
西西在吗？
Cici there?
哪里找？
Who's calling?
泰德
lt's Ted
你那无聊男友打来的
lt's your ill-conceived boyfriend
晚点见，别忘了设定警报器
Okay, l'll see you later And don't forget to set the alarm
喂，泰德
Hello, Ted
别痴心妄想泰德会打来 别忘了设警报器
You wish it was Ted Don't forget to set the alarm
喂
Hello?
不…求求你，不要
No! No! Please! No!
大家以为姐妹会的人 喜欢口交
Everyone thinks Sororitys are about blowjobs, but it's not true
不，我们只是提倡 安全性关系
We only promote safe condom sex
我们讲求爱，尊重与责任
We're about love respect and responsibility
吹萧也没关系，对吗？
Harmonica style is okay, right?
对
Yeah
鸡尾酒？
Cocktails?
你怎么拖这么久？
What took you so long?
德瑞克是我们的大哥哥
And you know Derek is a Delta Lambda big brother
我们要有一家人的感觉
And we like to keep it all in the family
你们真的教我太多了 谢谢
You girls have really given me a lot to think about. Thanks
有效
lt's working
宝贝，想跳舞吗？
Hey baby, wanna dance?
我很想…
l'd love to
跟那个高大宽肩的男生跳
With that tall wide shouldered Fraternity boy
真伤人
That hurts
帝国大反击 剧情效果都进步
Empire Strikes Back Better story, improved effects
不算续集，那是三部曲之一
Not a sequel. Party of a trilogy completely planned
我喜欢那些毛茸茸的小态
l like those little furry things
受不了
Ewoks・ ・ ・They blow
你怎么样？
How you doing? Good
傻妞们对你好吗？
Are the Twits being nice to you?
好得让人痛苦
Painfully nice
我想你不会入会了
l take it will not being pledging Delta Lambda Zeta
没错
l think not
干杯
Crushed
宿舍出事了 到处都是警察
Hey guys! Something is up at Omega Beta Zeta. The Police are everywhere
快
Hurry
真扫兴
What a way to break up a party
我应该带酒才对
Shit l should have brought my drink
这绝对不是自杀罗
So it's definitely not suicide
谢谢
Thank you
盖儿，你才刚来吗？
Gale, Hi. You're just getting here?
真不好，被害者是单身一人 姐妹会的女孩
lt's not good lt's a single victim. Sorority girl
我得走了，我快截稿了
l've got to go. l've got a deadline
乔，走
Joel, let's go
马上
ln a minute
又发生了，是不是
lt's happening again, isn't it?
你很高兴吧！不是吗？
You would love that, wouldn't you?
快去呀 独家会被抢走哦
Better hurry, Gale you might get scooped
快点，乔
Move it, Joel
我得跟你老实讲
Yeah, l have to be honest with you
我真的不行 我是来采访的
l'm not cut out for this. l was brought here to do an interview
不是来看杀人片
Not see ''Faces of Death 1 4?''
别他妈的扯东扯西
Do not fuck with me
来，拿外套，我送你回家
Come on, get your jacket Let's get you home
好
Yeah
好了吗？
Are you about ready?
马上好
Almost
喂
Hello?
喂，席妮，记得我吗？
Hello Sidney, Remember me?
你想干嘛？
What do you want?
我要你，好戏上场了
l want you, it's show time
那你怎么不露脸？ 他妈的孬种
Then why don't you show your face you fucking coward
真是我的荣幸
My pleasure
德瑞克
Derek
席妮
Sidney
德瑞克
Derek
是我，没事吧
lt's me! lt's me! Are you okay! You okay?
德瑞克，不要
Derek, don't
席妮
Sid
杜威
Dewey
杀手跟德瑞克在里面
The killer's in there, and Derek
你没事吧
Are you alright?
他往那边跑了
He went that way
到里面来
Sidney, get in here
都还好吧
ls everything okay?
他刺到我
He got me. He got me
压住伤口
Apply pressure to it
警察赶来了
The Police are on their way
谢谢你的合作
Thanks for your cooperation
我过几分种就来陪你
Hallie, l'll be with you in a few minutes, okay?
没问题
No problem
我犯罪生涯中 最简单的侦讯
Easiest interrogation of my crime filled life
我要去弄杯咖啡 你要吗？
l'm going to go get a cup of coffee You want?
你要吗？席妮
You want some, Sid?
你怎么样？还好吧
How you doing, are you all right?
一点也不好
Not at all
我早就知道没完没了
You know, l knew this was coming l knew this wasn't over
你不会孤军奋战的
You are not alone, Sid
不论你需要什么 我们都会陪你
We're all here for you Alright. Whatever you need
死掉的女孩真可怜
Poor girl
我知道，整件事都很疯狂
l know, it's crazy
德瑞克可能会被杀
Derek could have been killed you know
但他没有，他没事了
But he wasn't. He's fine
他该知道90年代 不能逞英雄
He just need to realize that the 90's are no time to play hero
他为什么要回到屋里？
Why did he go back into that house anyway?
我绕到屋后碰到席妮
l went around to the back of the house, and ran into Sid there
她说凶手在里面我就去看
That's when she told me the killer was inside. So l went into see・ ・ ・
你很幸运没伤到神经
You're lucky there is no nerve damage
这伤慢慢会恢复
You're going to have to take it easy though
然后你回到屋里
So then you went back inside the house
对
Yeah
没打斗，他割伤你就跑了？
No struggling he just cut you and ran away?
他没杀了你就算你走运
You're lucky he didn't kill you
对，要杀可容易的很
Yeah, it's awfully convenient
你说什么？
Say what?
没事，可惜轻易就让他逃走了
Nothing. lt's just a shame he got away so easily
可惜你太晚到
lt's just a shame you got there too late
他走了之后才出现
Right after he disappeared
是啊
Yeah, it is
有三名被害人
We have three victims
莫琳艾文斯，菲而史帝文斯
Maureen Evens, Phil Stevens
西西库伯
Cici Cooper
西西是真名吗？
ls Cici the girl's real name?
不是，是凯西库伯
No, it's Casey. Casey Cooper
跟凯西贝克一样？
As in Casey Becker?
你说什么？
Excuse me?
凯西贝克是伍兹镇的被害人
She was a young victim in Woodsboro
她男朋友史帝文奥斯也是
As well as her boyfriend Steven Orth
跟菲而史帝文斯一样
As in Phil Stevens
莫琳艾文斯 莫琳普瑞斯卡
Maureen Evens. Maureen Prescott
那是席妮的母亲
that's Sidney's mother
你想有人 在抄袭伍兹镇案？
Do you think someone's trying to duplicate Woodsboro?
看起来像
lt looks like it
这案子真的是模仿案
l think you have a copycat on your hands, Chief
天哪
Jesus Christ・ ・ ・
你要怎么让席妮安全？
What are you doing to keep Sidney safe?
我派了最优秀的刑警 保护她
l've got my two best detectives guarding her
这两人非得和你 寸步不离吗？
Do these guys have to follow you around everywhere?
我们是连体婴
We're attached at the hip
我要怎么才能跟你独处
How l am ever going to get you alone?
老实说
To be honest, Derek, l think it would be best to・ ・ ・
离我远点对你较好
your interest to stay as far away from me as possible
别因为情绪不好就说气话
Hope that was a off the cuff remark that holds no sub-text what so ever
其实我说真的
Actually, l mean it
瞧你，你已经受伤了
Look at you, you already got hurt
我不想再看到那种事发生
l don't want to see that happen again
我运气没那么背
l'll take my chances
我说真的，这很严重
Derek, l'm serious This is serious
你是担心我安危 还是不信任我
You are concerned with my personal well being. And not with ・ ・ ・
我猜对了吧？
trusting me or anything. Right?
我说了我不想看到你受伤
Like l said, l just don't want to see you get hurt
我也不想看你受伤，好吗？
And l don't want to see you get hurt. Okay Sid?
保重，魏小姐
Take care, Miss Weathers
杜威
Dewey
警长
Chief
我要去搜集资料 你要来吗？
Hi, l'm headed over to admissions to do some leg work, You game?
我可不帮你写书 我来帮席妮
l'm not here to write a book l'm here to help Sid
我也想帮她
l wanna help her too
当然也为了帮我自己
And help myself, of course
别这样，笑一个，拜托
Come on, Dewey Smile just once, please
等我抓到凶手也会笑
l'll smile when l catch the killer
盖儿，嗨
Gale, Hi
席妮的父亲没嫌疑了吗？
What about Sidney's father? Has he been ruled out as a suspect?
他出国了，这有点可疑
He's out of the country on business that sounds a little fishy.
你做你的调查，这和我无关
l'm not here to do your job Mrs Salt
杜威呢，他的出现有点怪
What about this ex-cop Dewey Riley? Kind of strange that he showed up
他来做什么？
What's he doing here?
杜威是好人 他和其他人不一样
Dewey's a good guy Unlike some of us
真的？
Really?
我只是觉得事件如果重演
lf the killer is repeating what happened in Woodsboro
凶手很可能是伍兹镇的人
lt could be quite possible that killer could be from Woodsboro
你想席妮会让我访问她吗？
Derek, do you think Sid would let me interview her for my documentary
她婉拒各大电视和新闻媒体
Didn't she turn down ''Primetime Live'', ''20-20'', and ''Dateline''
但可以为了你的纪录片
But for you, yeah
别闹了
Drop it
我在想谋杀的事
l've been thinking about his whole murder thing
你们查过蓝迪没有？
Have you checked out Randy?
什么？
What!
我知道他是无辜受害者
l know he's an innocent victim the first time around
但他有点怪，懂我意思吧！
But he's a little off You know what l'm saying?
蓝迪不会伤害人
Come on, Randy? The guy is harmless
许多杀人魔也都被这么认为
That's what they said about Damher
小声点
Guys, keep it down, come on
怎么了？席妮
What's up, Sid?
怎么了？
How's it going?
保镖刑警在哪里？
Where's the Secret Service guys?
那边
Over there
哪个是凯文科斯纳？
And which one is Kevin Costner?
右边的是李察警官
The one on the right is Officer Richard
魔羯座，离婚，有两个孩子
He is a Capricorn Divorced, father of Two
左边的是安德鲁警官
And the one on the left is Officer Andrews
双子座单身，我想是同性恋
He is a Gemini Single, but l think he's Gay
德瑞克，你要说什么
Derek, a penny for your thoughts?
早上醒来我有个感觉
This morning l woke up with this feeling
不知如何面对
l didn't know how to deal with
于是我决定藏在心里
And so l just decided to myself l'd hide it to myself
他在干嘛？
What is he doing?
汤姆克鲁斯，悍卫战士
Tom Cruise, Top Gun 1 986
德瑞克，不要
Derek, don't・ ・ ・
别这样
Don't do this
“我想我爱你”
l think l love you
“人生不就如此”
lsn't that what life is made of?
“我担心，我不曾有这种感受”
Though it worries me to say l've never felt this way
“我想我爱你，我怕什么”
l think l love you! So what am l so afraid of
“我怕不确定无药可救的爱”
l'm afraid that l'm not sure of A love there is no cure for
“我想我爱你，人生不就如此”
l think l love you lsn't that what life is made of
“我担心，我不曾有这种感受”
And though it worries me to say it l've never felt this way
“相信我，你不用担心”
Believe me, you don't have to worry
“我只想让你快乐”
l only want to make you happy
“如果你叫我走，我会走”
And if you say, hey go away! l will
“但我还是留下来爱你”
But l think l'd better stick around and love you
“直到你找到快乐”
Until you find happiness
让我问你，你真的爱我吗？
Let me ask you, do you think Do you really love me?
“因为我想我爱你”
Because l think l love you
各位同学，展现一点爱
Come on, people let's show a little love
别担心，席妮
Don't worry, Sid
我知道情况有点疯狂
l know things are a little crazy
那不是兄弟会的大忌吗？
lsn't that a big, Frat faux-pas?
对，万万不可
Yeah, that is a big no-no
不能把兄弟会信物送给女朋友
See, you're not suppose to give your Greek letters to your girl
不得以任何形式或方式
No shape, way or form
兄弟会修理他，但这是传统
The Brothers are gonna kick his ass But it's tradition
那是传统
lt's tradition
那是好运，它会保护你
lt's good luck lt will protect you
谈谈你这个广受争议的角色
So tell us about this part you're getting rave reviews for
我演席妮普瑞丝卡
l play this girl, Sidney Prescott
她发现她男友是疯狂杀人狂
Who discovers her boyfriend is a crazy serial killer
还在前一年杀了她母亲
who also killed her mother the year before that
你为角色下了多少功夫
So what kind of research did you do for the part?
我看了书…
l read the book・ ・ ・
他们竟让托莉史培林演席妮
They get Tori Spelling to play Sid
演我的却是无名小卒
And they cast Joe-Blow Nobody to play me
至少演你的还有些名气
At least you get David Schwimmer
演我的是珍西摩儿的马车夫
l get the guy who drove Jane Seymour's stagecoach in one episode of Doctor Quinn
以下是托莉演出的片段
Let's take a peak at the movie・ ・ ・
比利，你吓到我了，你干嘛！
Billy, you scared me what are you doing here?
我获释了，我是清白的
They let me go Sid l didn't do it. l'm innocent
我知道
l know
你为什么不让我碰你？
Why won't you let me touch you?
我最近碰到太多事
Look, l've been going through a lot lately, Billy
你要勇敢面对它好好活下去
Sid, l think you just need to deal with that and move on
我也要接受我妈离开我爸
When my mom left my dad, l accepted it.That's the way the cookie crumbles
妈妈总会离开我们
Moms leave
她离开镇上，不是埋在地下
Yeah, your mom left town. She's not buried in the cemetery somewhere
我妈死了，再也不会回来
My mom's dead and she's never coming back. Ever
笨
Stupid
我最爱看恐怖片
l love scary movies
我会等录影带上了再说
l'll wait for the video
好，谈正事
Okay, let's get down to business
我看马上就有人要怕续集
The way l see it someone's out to make a sequel
我们得搜集更多谋杀电影
You know, cash in on all the murder movie hoopla
所以我们要了解续集电影规则
So it's our job to observe the rules of a sequel
第一，死得更多
Number one the body count is always bigger
第二，死得更难看
Number two, the death scenes are always much more elaborate. More・ ・ ・
观众会期待更精彩的场面
blood, more gore. Carnage Candy Your core audience just expects it
第三
And number three・ ・ ・
想让续集卖座就千万别…
lf you want your sequel to become a franchise never, ever・ ・ ・
我只想知道怎么找到凶手
How do we find the killer, Randy? That's what l want to know
我们看看嫌犯
Let's look at the suspects
德瑞克，就像她前任男朋友
There's Derek the obvious boyfriend Hello Billy Loomis
他学医，用那点小伤搏取同情
The guy's pre-med and his pity-me service wound
那小伤完全避开了主要血管
conveniently missed every major vein and artery
你认为是德瑞克？
So you think it's Derek?
Not so fast
别太快下断语
假设凶手是有点小聪明
Let's assume the killer or killers have half a brain
他就不会去重蹈覆辙
He's not a ''Nick at Night'' re-run type of guy
他要另外再找新点子
He wants to break some new ground Right?
别管男友，太老套了，还有谁
forget the boyfriend lt's tired. Who else do we got?
米奇，那个昆汀塔伦提诺迷
Mickey The freaky Tarantino film student
如果他是 那我也有嫌疑，再想
But if he is a suspect So am l. So let's move on
等一下，搞不好你正是嫌犯
Let's not move on Maybe you are a suspect
我是嫌犯，那你也是
lf l'm a suspect, you're a suspect
有理
You have a point
好，继续
Okay, let's move on
海莉
Hallie
席妮的室友？
Sid's roommate?
典型杀人狂是白种男性
Serial killers are typically white males
这样才完美，违反规则
That's why it's perfect. lt's sort of against the rules, but not really
黑人小姐是绝佳的杀人狂
Mrs. Voohies was a terrific serial killer
总得给黑人小姐一个机会
And there's always room for Candy Man's daughter
她甜美，所以危险
She's sweet. She's deadly She's bad for your teeth
拜托，这些人是你朋友
Come on, Randy These kids are your friends
你认为谁是凶手
Who do you think is the killer?
魏盖儿怎么样？
How about Gale Weathers?
盖儿，凶手？
Gale, a killer?
为什么不？
Why not?
她心眼够坏
She's vicious enough
她只是个机会主意者
She's an opportunist
想不到吗？她在筹备下一本书
lsn't it conceivable She's planning her next book
记者最会炒新闻了
That's what reporters do Dewey. They stage the news
不，盖儿绝不会是凶手
No, Gale's a lot of things but Gale's not a killer
你太迷恋她了
Just because you're sweet on her
我没有
l'm not
拜托，我是蓝迪哎
Please, this is me talking, Randy
我是单恋席妮的爱情奴隶耶
The unrequited love slave of Sidney Prescott
我知道什么是执迷不误
l know all about obsession
这很痛苦
and pain
你有爱的伤疤来证明
And you've got your love scar to prove it
你也有
And so do you
你怎么会跛脚？ 因为你被刺到背
Man, what is with that limp anyway? 'Cause you were stabbed in the back
因为神经被切断
Severed nerve
但盖儿绝不是凶手
Look, Gale's no killer
好，随便你怎么说
Okay, okay, whatever you say
她不是凶手，就是目标
But if she's not a killer she's a target
乔，拍一些背景画面
Joel, let's get some establishing shots
可以谈一下吗？
Gale, can we talk for a second?
什么事？
What is it?
我搞不懂 以你过去的遭遇
Look, l'm a little confused here l mean, with your track record
现在又发生凶案 何必在这逗留
Why would you want to be here when the killer strikes again?
我应该在接下工作前 看你的书
l mean granted, l should have read your book. Before l took this job
我正在看，哇
But, l'm reading it now, and whoa
才知道前一个摄影师的下场
l read what happened to your last cameraman
他被开膛剖肚
The guy got gutted
我现在要做一般人会做的事
Now me? l would do what any rational human being should do
那就是走人
Which is get the fuck out of here
他没被开膛剖肚 那是我编的
First of all, he wasn't gutted l made that up
他是喉咙被割断
His throat was slashed
反正他已不在人世了
Gale, gutted-slashed the guy ain't in the union no more
这是工作
lt's a job, Joel
所有工作都有一些风险
And like every job there's a few drawbacks
你是专业摄影师就敬业点
You're a professional cameraman You've got to act like one
我只想报新闻 不想变成新闻
Yeah, but l want to report the news l don't want to be the news
黑人在这种情况下 都活不久
Besides, ''Brothers'' don't last long in situations like this
这是全国电视网
This is national television
这是成名的大好良机
Think about it This is a big chance for you
你不想参与 轰动全国的报导？
The story is monumental Don't you want to be a part of that?
我需要你，没你我做不到
Come on, l need you l cannot do this without you
好，干活吧
Good, come on Let's get some work done
好，准备去被宰吧
Yeah, let's go get killed
我们先前谈过了
We've been through this before
你知道我认为 你很有表演潜力
You know what l think of your potential as an actress
我知道，只是命案的事
l know it's just that with the murders
那部电影和我的人生都一团乱
And the movie, and my life
我知道这对你很困难
l do know how difficult it is for you
我觉得我做不到
Gil, l just don't think l can do it
你必须利用艺术来化解忧虑
The battle for the soul is fought in the forum of the art
你是斗士，所以你在这儿
You're a fighter Sid That's why you're here
所以你会主修戏剧
That's why this is your major
对，我是斗士
Yeah, l'm a fighter
我没听到
l didn't hear that
我是斗士
l'm a fighter
我不相信你
l don't believe you
我不信
l don't
我是斗士
l'm a fighter
好
Okay
我知道这样说太LKK了
So at the risk sounding like a college drama teacher
但我要利用这种痛苦
if you have pain around this type of material, use it
这是你的角色
This is your role, Sid
卡珊德拉是悲剧性 的预言家
Cassandra is one of the great tragic visionaries of literature
她全预料到了
She saw it all coming
战争，谋杀，疯狂
The wars, the murder, the madness
她知道她被诅咒
She knew she was cursed
那是她的宿命，她拥抱它
lt was her fate and she embraced it
宿命难逃，但身为艺术家
None of us can avoid our fate But as an artist・ ・ ・
你能诚实的面对它，对抗它
you can honestly face it and fight it
你真行
You're good
没替角，我一定要说服你
There's no understudy l'm desperate
你做得到的
You can do this
好，大家集合，第三幕
Okay, everybody gather around third act, one last time
音乐来
Cue the music
看，特洛伊城可怕的恶运
Behold the dreaded fate of Troy
曾伫立照亮斯巴达的山坡
That once stood proud and light upon the hills of Sparta
如今笼罩在废墟的烟雾中
Now shrouded in the deathly smoke of ruin
其王室子女从墙上被抛下
Her royal children picthed from her walls
子民从废墟中被驱赶而过
Her people driven through her ruins
卡珊德拉孤独站在残忍宿命中
And now, alone in Fate's cruel isolation stands Cassandra
她的王国，家人和朋友
Her kingdom, family and friends
被赶到大门口
driven to the gate
我未犯下反神之罪
No crime against God or man have l committed
除了说出真相
Save to speak the truth
我心中的可怕预言皆已降临
And each hideous vision born from my mind has come to pass
特洛伊沦陷了
Troy has fallen
不是藉我的手或愿望
Not by my hand, or wish
而是如我预见的
But as l foresaw
如今宿命复仇之眼
So now, Fate's vengeful eye・ ・ ・
盯上了...我
is fixed ・ ・ ・on me
告诉我们，卡珊德拉
Tell us O Cassandra
生命的甜美如今何在
where has the sweetness of life gone?
如何让宿命之手不攻击你
What stays fate's hand from striking now at three?
好，暂停
Alright, hold it
暂停
Hold it
大家休息一下
Everyone take five
席妮
Sidney?
你的护花使者来了
Sid. Your escort has arrived
德瑞克，你来多久了？
Derek, how long have you been here?
刚到，还好吧？ 怎么回事？
l just got here. ls everything okay what's going on?
米奇呢？
What happened to Mickey?
我们调换，他要剪接
We swapped. He had to edit
我来接，怎么了？
You get me instead. What happened?
不要…
Derek, don't・ ・ ・
我现在需要独处，好吗？
l just l need to be alone right now. Okay?
独处不是办法
Being alone is not the answer, Sid
我的意思是我需要距离
Yeah, l think it is l need some distance
我还能说什么？
Well, do l get a say in this?
别说了
No
我知道我该体谅你
l guess l'm supposed to be understanding
没错
Yeah
没问题
You got it
如果凶手在重演 伍兹镇血案
Alright, let's just assume that the killer is repeating Woodsboro
喂
Yes?
我再打给你
l have to call you back
那他干嘛要攻击席妮
That doesn't explain Sidney's attack
她在伍兹镇又没被杀掉
Sidney wasn't killed in Woodsboro
她只是逃过一劫
lt wasn't for a lack of trying
凶手想做个了结
The killer is trying to finish what was started
席妮有人保护，对吗？
Sid is under protection, right?
对
Yeah
干嘛？
What?
跟鲍伯说我会打给他
Tell Bob l'll call him back
她几时开始抽烟了？
When did she start smoking?
从网路上出现 她的裸照开始
Ever since those nude pictures on the lnternet
那是我的头，玛丹娜的身体
lt was just my head lt was Jennifer Aniston's body
我们一定忘了什么重点
Anyway, you're forgetting something
在伍兹镇有更多被害人
ln Woodsboro, there were more victims before the home stretch
泰坦，他是我的摄影师
Tatum, my cameraman, Himbry
暂停，我不想听摄影师的事
Time out. See l don't need to be hearing about no dead cameraman
我警告你们，我要闪人了
Now l'm warning you guys, l'm a verb away from vacating these premises
我去买咖啡 甜甜圈和镇定剂
l'm gonna go get me some coffee, donuts, Prozac
看能不能找到一些快乐丸
See if l can find some crack special K, Eggs
等你们谈完我再回来
l'll be back when you guys start talking about something little more ''Save By The Bellish'' Alright?
他好像很害怕
He seems a little shaky
别担心他
Don't worry about him
我们要找出凶手杀人模式
lf the killer is following a pattern
看谁是下一个受害者
then maybe we can figure out who is next
没有模式 我们都被追杀过
That wouldn't follow the pattern we were all involved in Woodsboro
我们任何一个 都可能被害
lt could be anyone of us
好，那你想怎样？
Okay so what do you want to do, Bonehead?
等着看下一个是谁吗？ 蠢蛋
You just want to sit here and wait for who drops next?
我不知道，电话小姐
l don't know, phonehead
盖儿不在
Gale's not here
打搅你们吗？ 你们好像很烦恼
l'm not interrupting anything, am l You three look deep in thought
尝过刀子割肉的滋味吗？
Have you ever felt a knife cut through human flesh and scrape the bone beneath?
是他
lt's him
谁？
Who?
凶手，他看得到我们
The killer! He can see us
别让他挂电话
Just keep him on the phone
我要跟他说什么？
What do you want me to say?
不知道，让他继续讲，走
l don't know. Just keep him talking. Come on, Gale
我们要干嘛？
What are we doing?
找有行动电话的人
Look for somebody with a cell-phone
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
So, what's your favorite scary movie?
你们绝对找不到我
You'll never find me
你怕什么？ 让他们去玩
What do you care let them have their fun
那你要干嘛？
So, what's up?
你最喜欢哪部恐怖片？
What's your favorite scary movie?
“美国舞娘”吓死人了
Show girls. Absolutely frightening
你呢？
What's yours?
对不起
Sorry・ ・ ・
你要干嘛？
What's your problem?
等等，让我猜，惊魂夜
Wait, let me guess The House on Sorority Row?
滴血校舍，溅血校园
Dorm that dripped Blood? Splatter University?
结业日，期终考
Graduation Day? Final Exam?
我很接近你吗？
Am l close?
比你想像中近
Closer than you think
猜错了，你想死吗？
Too slow you Geek Do you want to die?
这已经是你最厉害 的招数啦？
ls that the best you can do?
第一集的凶手 都比你有创意
Because Billy and Stu were much more original
你是哪位？
Who's this?
伍兹镇血案的作者魏盖儿
Gale Weathers author of the Woodsboro Murders
谁？
Who?
好，他一定在这附近
Okay, he's got to be around here someplace
他在耍我们
He's just playing with us
白种男性嫌犯 九点种方向
White male suspect nine o'clock
我的表或你的表？
My clock or your clock
你的表，绕到后面
Your clock. Go around the back
你来干嘛？ 你绝不会是男主角
Why are you even here Randy? You'll never be the leading man
去你的
Fuck you
你再努力也当不了英雄
No matter how hard you try you'll never be the hero
而且永远无法得到席妮
And you'll never ever get the girl
妈的，对不起
Shit! Sorry・ ・ ・
倒霉鬼，死人
Wrong guy, dead boy
是吗？ 想重新再杀人一次吗？
Oh yeah? Let's redirect mister
我很有创意哦
''l'm so original''
搞什么鬼？
What the hell are you doing?
抱歉，对不起
Sorry, Beg your pardon
你的创意在哪？
Where's your innovation?
干嘛模仿两个 高中窝囊废
Why copy-cat two High School looser-ass dick heads
史都是没种的娘娘腔
Stu was a pussy-ass wet rag
而比利鲁米斯，搞什么
And Billy Loomis! Billy Loomis! What the fuck?
獐头鼠目 性压抑又黏着妈妈
Jesus! What a rat-looking homo repressed mama's boy
目标订高点，想当大人物吗？
Why not set your goals higher You want to be one of the big boys?
辛普森，高天民，陈进兴
Manson? Bundy? OJ?
蓝迪在哪？
Where's Randy?
没看到他
l don't see him
蓝迪
Randy
怎么回事？
What's going on?
谁把我的车窗打破了
Who broke my window?
你的电脑不动了吗？
Did your computer just freeze?
你有讯息，按ALT一M
You have an instant message that's all. Just hit Alt-M
可是我还没上线
Yeah, but l'm not signed on
所有终端机都有连线
Someone here in the library all the terminals are connected
“你今晚会死”
他在这边
He's here
“警察救不了你” 把她带开，可能是病态的玩笑
Get her away from the computer Sid, it's probably just a sick joke
在这边等
Wait right here, okay
你还好吗？
Sid, are you okay?
卡顿
Cotton?
可以谈一下吗？
Can we talk for a second?
现在不是时候
This isn't a good time
别这样，是你害我坐牢的
Come on Sid, you sent me to prison
坐一年牢 不能给我两分种
lt's been over a year for you you can give me two minutes
我很遗憾 我不知该如何道歉
Cotton, l'm sorry. Everyday l'm sorry. l don't know how to apologize
别遗憾，我给你道歉的方式
Don't be sorry, sorry-shmory. l have a solution to all our problems
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
别管魏盖儿，她什么都不懂
First of all, forget Gale Weathers
她不明白你我之间的故事
She doesn't get it. She doesn't see the story between you and me
即使凶手杀了她 她都不知为什么
She wouldn't see the story if it smacked her in the side of the head
重点是你知道谁找我吗？
Which brings me to my point Who calls me out of the blue?
黛安索而，够吓人吧
Diane Sawyer. Believe me Sid l was as shocked as you are
我们可以有 整整一小时的节目
lf you and l go on the air together She will give us the entire hour
而且是黄金时段
We are talking Prime Time, Sid You, me and Diane Sawyer
我做不到
Cotton, l can't
他们付我们一人一万块
lf this is about money lt's not like we're not getting paid $1 0,000 dollars each
更别提 还有计费的CALL IN
Not to mentioned what l got going on the side with the #900 number
我知道你不喜欢媒体
l know. You don't like the press
我很尊重你，可是席妮…
l know that and l respect it But Sidney
这是黛安索而哎
lt's Diane Sawyer. Hello?
她很大牌，曝光率会很高
She's a class act. This could be some very, very heavy exposure
对不起
l'm sorry
大家都从电影和书知道真相
Look, between the movie, & the book People know the truth
曝光够多了，你还要怎样
Let's get on our lives There's been enough exposure
不能平静地生活吗？
Why would you want anymore?
要怎样？我不知道哎
Why? l don't know, Sidney
我想更出名吧！
Maybe because l fucking deserve a little exposure
别这样，是你先毁掉我的名誉
Come on Sidney, you drag my name through the mud
让大家都以为我是变态凶手
Everybody thinks l'm some kind of Psycho killer
我只是要求做个访问
& all l'm asking for is one little fucking Diane Sawyer interview
让我澄清我的罪名
To maybe give my side of the story straight
这不会太不近人情吧？
l don't think l'm being unreasonable in that request. Do you honestly?
抱歉，不行
l'm sorry, Cotton, but no
你抱歉
You are sorry
我敢说你真的很抱歉
l bet you're real sorry, Sidney
你到底想怎样？
What's your angle, Sidney?
可爱倒霉的 席妮普瑞斯卡
Lovable and fucked up Sidney Prescott
最受欢迎的受害人
Everybody's favorite little victim
你们做什么？
What are you doing?
天哪，我不是比利
Jesus! l'm not Billy Loomis
他杀了她，他死了 记得吗？
she killed him, he's dead, remember?
再跟我讲一遍，好吗？
Run it by me one more time Will you?
你为什么攻击席妮？
Why did you attack Sidney Prescott
哪有攻击 只是谈得很激烈
There was not attack We were talking, very heatedly
席妮和我 有段复杂的过去
Miss Prescott and l have a very complicated past
和她有口角不算犯罪
l didn't think that was a crime
没有 若有谋杀意图就有罪
No, but homicide is
那就收押我
Then book me. Book me
谋杀的事我不懂
Okay? Look l don't know about homicide
但你们因为 我在图书馆喧哗而抓我
But you defiantly got me for raising my voice in a public library
这是四起命案 讲话当心点
We're dealing with four murders here. You watch your mouth
不该杀蓝迪，应该杀我
lt shouldn't have been Randy lt should have been me
我应该打给他母亲
l should call his mother
我打过了
Sid, l already made that phone call
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我没那么脆弱，轻易被击倒
Stop treating me like glass, Dewey l'm not going to break
有时脆弱一点没关系
lt's okay to break
我不会让它表现出来
lt's not going to happen
你最好有充分的不在场理由
You better hope your alibi is air-tight
容我提醒各位我是清白的
Could l please remind everyone here that l'm an innocent man
你们不看2100全民开讲吗？
Don't you watch TV ''Current Edition''
很犀利的电视节目
That was a very insightful program On which it was made abundantly・ ・ ・
这节目明白指出过我的清白
clear that l'm an innocent man
除非你们亲眼目睹 我持刀杀人
So until you find me standing over a dead body with a knife in my hand
否则请给我个公道
l think you better treat me with the rights and privileges accorded to every citizen in this country
还是你们不了解 什么叫无辜？
ls there some problem with the word innocent
很重要的字，警长？是吧
l don't know lt's a big one, Chief?
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我们得放他走
We're going to let him go
为什么？
Why?
没证据关他
We don't have anything on him
在这边签名
Sign here
盖儿
Gale
戏好看吗？ 警察真可笑
enjoying the show? Cops are funny
你在做什么？
What do you think you're doing?
等你访问我十五分种，懂吧
Waiting for my 1 5 minutes of fame You can understand that, can't you?
别做傻事，卡顿
Don't do anything stupid, Cotton
你帮了大忙让我自由
You were so instrumental in my freedom
你不会是后悔吧
You're not having character doubts now, are you?
席妮，如果你改变心意…
Sidney, if you change your mind ・ ・ ・
好了，让开吧！
Come on, take a hike
真遗憾遇到这个怪胎
Sorry about that. What a creep
我们带你到安全的地方
We're going to take you somewhere safe, Sid
好，哪里？
Yeah, where's that?
不知道，但我会陪着你
l don't know But l'll be there with you
应该走了
We should get going
我们会载你到宿舍 收拾东西
Take you by the dorm and you can pack some things
警方今晚封锁了校园
We've issued a campus lock-in this evening
天黑后不准有人进出
No one is allowed out after dark. Okay.
会是谁这么做？
Who's doing this, Dewey?
除了卡顿还有谁？
lf not Cotton, then who?
不知道，但我会找到他
l don't know, Sid but l'll find him
有线索吗？ 凶手会找上你吗
Any leads, Gale? Do you think the killer will come after you?
换你变成新闻主角感觉如何？
How does it feel to be on the other side of the news?
卡顿，你还是嫌犯吗？
Cotton! Are you still a suspect?
那是天大的误会
lt's all been a huge misunderstanding
你正式获释了吗？
Cotton have you been officially released?
盖儿，等等 拍张照吧
Gale, hold on a second How about a photo?
不要？ 你很上相哎
No? You look great
你还好吗？
How you holding up, Gale? lt must be scary・ ・ ・
被窥伺的感觉 一定很恐怖吧！
knowing somebody's out there waiting, watching, enjoying all this
你做何感想…
How does that make you feel?
我知道你把我 当做踏脚石
Look, local woman! l know you hold me up as your career template
挑战我让你想利用我 一步登天
And it give you some sort of charge to challenge me
还早的很呢！
But give it a rest
你说得对，抱歉
You're right. l'm sorry
时候不对，对不起
lt was, the wrong time. l'm sorry
怎么回事？
What's going on?
你瞧！他们扣押了我的车
Let's see, for starters they impounded my van
多亏你 它成了命案现场
it's now an official crime scene Thanks to you
这是你的影片
Here is your footage
你自个儿慢慢看 我要走了
Enjoy. See ya wouldn't want to be ya
乔，我需要你
Joel, l need you
不，你需要检查脑袋
No, you need to have your head examined
我觉得很惨
l feel bad, Dewey
我觉得惨透了
l feel really bad
我从不认为我会这么惨！
l never say that because l never feel bad about anything
但我现在觉得很惨
But l feel bad now
这是魏盖儿分身 的真情演出吗？
ls this just another brilliant Gale Weathers Performance?
又没人在拍我 我只是想找凶手
There's no cameras here l just want to find this fucker
我真的想
l really do
我也想
Me too
我能帮你吗？
Can l give you a hand?
里面是什么？
What's in here?
乔拍的群众影片
Just some crowd footage that Joel shot
等一下
Wait a minute
若凶手 真的无时不刻的窥伺
lf the killer really is watching and relishing every minute
那他就会在带子上 对吗？
Then he would be here on these tapes, right?
在每个犯罪现场
At each crime scene
值得看一看
lt's worth a look
肯定值得一看
Definitely worth a look
这边
This way
配音室
Dubbing room
剪接室，录影档案
editorial. Video archive
锁住了
lt's locked
你能撬开吗？
Can you pick it?
那就是私闯
That would be breaking and entering
真的
No shit
这附近一定有录影机
There's got to be a VCR around here somewhere
那里面是什么
What's in there?
有进展了
Now we're getting somewhere
太好了
Perfect
从这卷开始
Let's start with this one
抱歉
Sorry
对不起
l'm sorry
弄痛你没？
Did l hurt you?
没有
No
你贪图名利，原谅我直说
You're a money hungry, fame seeking
也是笔法二流的作家
and forgive me for saying mediocre writer
而且冷酷无情
who's got a cold storage shed where her heart should be
别见怪
No offense intended
你生气的样子很可爱
You're cute when you're angry
我不是有意的
l was being rude
杜威，很抱歉
Dewey, l'm sorry
我从没想过伤害你
l never meant to hurt you
真的
Really
我得K书，我要交生物作业…
l should be studying you know l got a bio・ ・ ・
杜威
Dewey
对不起
Sorry
那不是我的影片
That's not my footage
去你的
Fuck you
你再努力也当不了英雄
No matter how hard you try you'll never be the hero
而且永远无法赢得芳心
And you'll never ever get the girl
找错人了，死猪
Wrong guy, dead boy
别走开
Stay here
杜威，不要
Dewey, don't!
杜威
Dewey
那边没人
There's no one there
操
Fuck
盖儿，盖儿
Gale! Gale?
盖儿
Gale
不
No
那么…
So・ ・ ・
听着，席妮
Listen, Sid
嘿，等等
Wait up
她没关系
She's fine
我是她的心理医师
l'm her therapist
拜，德瑞克
Bye, Derek
我们最好走了
We better get going
等这一切过去了
When this is all over
我还会在这儿
l'll still be here
你，准备受死吧
You! Prepare to Die
你把兄弟会的信物送人了
You gave up your letters
好浪漫
So romantic
绝对希腊风味
Totally so Greek
好冷
That's cold
宝贝，你爱谁？
Who do you love, baby! Sidney
你是说爱我们兄弟会吗
Did you say my Omega Kappa Beta brothers?
不，我说爱席妮
No, l said Sidney
你们要带我们到哪？
So where you taking us anyway?
说出来 我们就得杀了你们
lf we told you we'd have to kill you
别问，别讲
Don't ask, don't tell
下车，你这个混蛋
Out of the car, you fucker
趴下
Get down back there
王八蛋，我会让你脑袋开花
Pull it over, you son of a bitch l'll blow your fucking head off
他死了吗？
ls he dead?
我不认为
l don't think so
他还在呼吸
No, he's still breathing
他死了吗？
ls he dead?
天哪，我想是
Oh God, l think so
怎么离开这里？
How you suppose to get out of here?
不可能，这是警车
We are not, it is a cop car
帮我弄
Help me with this We're jammed up against the wall
我的天
Oh my God
不要，席妮，不要
Don't・ ・ ・ Sid ・ ・ ・
我讨厌这种事
God, l hate this shit
我的天，别再来一遍
Oh my God, don't do that again
从窗子
Through the window
该死
Shit
卡住了，你得从前面出来
lt's jammed, you're going to have to go through the front
休想
No fucking way
海莉，快点
Hallie. Do it・ ・ ・Hallie, do it
好，很好
Okay, that's good
走吧
Come on, let's go
海莉
Hallie
干嘛？
What?
我想知道是谁
l want to know who it is
不，席妮，求求你
No, Sid, come on, please
我要回去看
l'm going back
智障才回去，有点脑袋都会逃
Look, look, stupid people go back Smart people run
我们有脑袋，快逃命啦
we are smart people. So we should get the fuck out of here
我逃烦了
Hallie, l'm sick of running
不查明凶手会没完没了
lf we know who it is it's all over
可以找警察啊！
We can just get the police
等警察来他早跑了
Yeah, and when we come back he'll be gone
一下就好
lt will only take a minute l have to
席妮，不要，回来
Sid, no Sid, come back
席妮，回来
Sid, come back
该死
Shit
怎么了？
What?
他不见了
He's gone
什么？
What?
盖儿
Gale?
离我远一点
Get away from me
不…不是你想的那样
No, no This isn't want it looks like
我发现杜威，我想救他
l found Dewey. l tried to help him
盖儿，等等
Gale! Wait! Gale
妈的
Shit
救命啊！
Help me
电话给我
Give me the phone
我正在做报导
l was in the middle of a story
我有你要的报导
l have your God damned story
怎么了？
What's the matter?
这是急事，帮我接警察
Operator, this is an emergency get me the police
发生什么事？
What's happening?
凶手是卡顿威瑞
The killer is Cotton fucking Weary
卡顿威瑞？
Cotton Weary?
哈罗
Hello?
有人吗？
Hello!
Hello?
有人吗？
天哪，德瑞克
God. Derek
德瑞克
Derek
谢天谢地，席妮
Thank you, thank God, Sid
我以为我会在这 待到公演当晚
T thought l was going to be up there until opening night
谁绑的？ 我们得离开这边
Shit. Who tied these? We have to get out of here
兄弟们抓住我
Brothers got me, Sid
他在追我 他杀了海莉
Derek, he's after me He killed Hallie
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
凶手在这边
The killer. He's here
哪边？
Where?
就是这边
Right here
你动作很快嘛！
You're fast, Sid
把我弄下来
Get me down
换成是我 我不会那么做
l wouldn't do that if l were you
你当真要信任 男朋友吗？
You really want to trust your boyfriend?
你不知道历史会重演吗？
Don't you know history repeats itself. Sid
米奇
Mickey
没想到吧！席妮！
Surprise, Sidney
搞什么？
What the fuck?
都是德瑞克不配合好
Since Derek here disappeared on my ass
害我整晚都一个人
l've been on my own all the fucking night
多谢你哦，伙伴
Thanks a lot, partner
王八蛋，他疯了
You mother fucker! Sid, he's crazy
你知道我不会那样的！
You know me better than that
我必须有搭档
Sid, l've got to have a partner
我一个人是做不来的
l couldn't possibly done this alone
德瑞克
Derek
不，席妮，不…
No, Sid. No・ ・ ・
没关系，我们抓到她了
lt's okay, Derek. We got her
他在说谎
Sid, he's lying
席妮，我跟你说，帮我松绑
Sid! l'm telling you, Sid. Untie me
男朋友？ 凶手？
Boyfriend, killer? Boyfriend, killer?
他在说谎 把我松绑
Sid, the man is lying! Untie me Sid, untie me
你觉得怎样？ 似曾相识吗？
What do you think, Derek? Sidney experiencing some dejavu?
我会杀了你，杀了你
l am going to fucking kill you Fucking kill you
你死定了
You are dead! Dead!
真对不起
l'm so sorry
我绝不会伤害你
l never would have hurt you
绝不会
Never
你得搞清楚 谁才值得信任
You should really deal with your trust issues, Sid
可怜的德瑞克
l mean, poor Derek
很无辜，这么好的人
He's completely innocent and such a nice guy too
聪明，风趣又英俊
He's bright, funny and handsome
歌声还可以的准医生
Decent singing voice and he was going to be a doctor
你会想带回家 给妈妈看的男孩
This was the kind of boy you'd like to take home to Mom
如果你有妈
lf you have a Mom
去你的
Fuck you
喔，这么凶！
Oh! So vulgar
比利让你那样讲话吗？
Billy let you talk to him this way?
比利跟你一样变态！
Billy was a sick fuck Just like you
不，比利想逃避制裁
No, Billy was a sick fuck who tried to get away with it
而米奇想被抓到
Mickey is a sick fuck who wants to get caught
我的法庭抗辩 都计划好了
Yeah! l've got my whole defense Planned out
我可以把罪过 推在电影头上
l'm going to blame the movies
很酷吧，以前没人做过
Pretty cool, huh? lt hasn't been done before
现在只是审判前的开场白
You see this is just the beginning A prelude to the trial
审判才是我的重头戏
That's where the real fun is.'Cause these days it's all about the trial
因为电影暴力 对社会的影响
Can you see it? Effects of cinema violence on society
我会请大律师代表我
l'll get Dershovitz Cochran to represent me
谢长廷会在证人席为我辩护
Bob Dole on the witness stand in my defense
基督教联盟会付诉讼费用
Hell, the Christian Coalition will pay my legal fees
太完美了
lt's airtight, Sid
我是无辜的受害人
l'm an innocent victim
你疯了
You're a psychotic
对，那是我们的小秘密
Yeah that will be our little secret
民众喜欢精彩的审判
People love a good trial
跟戏剧一样，他们爱死了
lt's like theater they're dying for it
我必须满足观众
Now l've worked hard to give the audience what they want
比利真厉害 他知道这跟手法有关
That's what Billy was good at He knew, it's all about execution
是吗？你忘了一件比利的事
Yeah? you are forgetting our thing about Billy Loomis
什么事？
What's that?
我杀了他
l fucking killed him
席妮，你想学银幕女英雄
Sid. You got a Linda Hamilton thing going
这样好，我喜欢
No, no, it's nice. l like it
是谁搞的鬼！
Now who's doing that!
是久候的神秘佳宾吗？
Could that be the mystery guest waiting in the wings?
我说过我有拍档，真相揭晓！
Told you l had a partner, Sid Surprise cameo just for you
盖儿！
Gale
鲁米斯太太
Mrs Loomis?
什么？
What?
比利的母亲
Billy's mother
够曲折吧！ 敲破头也猜不到吧！
Nice twist, huh? Didn't see it coming, did you?
不可能，我看过你的照片
lt can't be l've seen pictures of you
减肥60磅 花了不少功夫
Lose sixty pounds and a lot of work later
我去媚登峰 相信我你也做得到
lt's called a make-over You should try it
你看起来有点疲倦
You look a little tired there yourself, Gale
你们俩一伙的？
So you two were in this together?
我需要资助，学费很贵
Yeah, had to have financing Tuition's expensive
黛比支持我
Deb' there, my backer
我们在神经病网站认识的
We met on the lnternet Psycho-website
极机密的
classifieds
据估计国内只有97个杀人狂
There's only an estimated 97 active serial killers in the country today
找到米奇真棒，他前途无量
So Mickey here was quite a find Definitely one on the way up
只需要一点引导和教育
All he needed was a little guidance and nurturing
这就是母爱的光辉
As only a mother can do
我跟你说会成功吧
Told you this was going to work
等到法庭审判时 会更惊天动地
Wait till the trial lt's gonna rock
米奇，不会有审判的
Mickey there's not going to be a trial
盖儿
Gale
一石二鸟
Two birds. One stone
米奇是个好孩子
Mickey was a good boy
他老把罪过推给电影
but my God that old blame the movies motive
你相信吗？
Did you buy that for a second?
这可怜的孩子彻底疯了
Poor boy was completely out of his mind
而你没有？
And you're not?
不，我很清醒
No. l'm very sane
我的动机没像米奇那么90年代
My motive isn't as nineties as Mickey
我是老套的复仇记
Mine is just good old fashioned revenge
你杀了我儿子
You killed my son
我杀你是再合理不过的事
And now l kill you. And l can't think of anything more rational
你逃不过制裁的
You're never going to get away with this
当然会
Of course l will
一切线索都追溯到米奇身上
Everything is traceable back to Mickey
包括他用来杀人的警察配枪
lncluding the cop-gun he used to kill everybody
假设你拿到另一把枪
But let's just suppose you had gotten hold of the other cop's gun
你追米奇，一场枪战扭打
You chased Mickey and there was a big shoot out. Big scuffle
你杀了米奇，米奇挂了
And you shot Mickey Killed Mickey dead
但他先前对你开了一枪
But not before he got off one shot at you
我都顾到了吗？ 有问题吗
Okay. Have l covered everything? Are there any questions?
你还问我意见啊！
Any comments? You know what though
反正谁在乎
Who gives a flying fuck anyway
让他们去追第二个凶手
Let them try and track down the second possible killer
黛比索特根本不存在
Debbie Salt doesn't exist
你跟你儿子一样疯
You're as crazy as your son was
你说什么？
What did you just say?
那是藐视我儿子的话吗？
Was that a negative disparaging remark about my son? About my Billy!
不，比利是个好孩子
No, Billy was a good boy
比利很完美 你教得很好
Billy was perfect you did a bang-up job, Mrs. Loomis
少拍我马屁 我手中有枪
lt's not wise to patronize a woman with a gun, Sidney
蓝迪贬低比利 捅他真爽
Randy spoke poorly of Billy and l got a little knife happy
我是个好母亲
l was a good mother
你知道我最恨什么吗？
You know what makes me sick
我恨人家说
l'm sick to death of people saying that it's all the parent fault
都是父母的错
That it all starts with the family
如果要怪 怎么不怪你妈
Want to blame someone? Why don't you blame your mother?
偷走我老公 破坏我的家庭
She's the one that stole my husband And broke up my family
然后你又抢走我儿子
And then you took my son
你不知道当母亲的滋味
You don't know what it is to be a mother
养育孩子 教他，开导他
To raise a child To teach him! And guide him
遗弃他
And abandon him
米奇不是死了吗？
lsn't Mickey supposed to be dead?
不准动，可恶
Don't you fucking move God damn it
卡顿
Cotton
好，大家慢下来
Okay, okay. Everybody slow down
我今天非常非常倒霉
l have had a very very bad day
我想知道怎么回事，席妮
& l would like to know exactly what the fuck is going on here! Sidney?
这是比利的母亲 她是凶手
Cotton, meet Billy Loomis' mother she's the killer
什么？
What?
那是谁？
And who's that?
另一个凶手，米奇
The other killer, Mickey
好
Okay
卡顿
Look, Cotton
闭嘴
Shut up
那么…嗨
So・ ・ ・Hi
你不是黛比索特对吗？
You're not Debbie Salt, are you?
你不是邮电报的人
You're not with the Post Telegraph?
没错，但我还是能帮你
No, but l can still help you Cotton
你不需要他 让我杀了她
You don't need her Let me killer her
她活着你就当不了主角
As long as she's alive, you're never going to be the lead story
那是你要的，不是吗？
That's what you really want lsn't it, Cotton?
想要曝光出名 就让我杀了她
lf you really want the spotlight Just let me killer her. Right now
你是唯一生还者，你是明星
Then you're the only survivor You're the star
她害你坐了一年牢
She sent you to prison for a year
听起来很顺耳吧
Personally l think it's rather poetic
卡顿，别听她的
No, Cotton, don't you listen to her
很难做决定，不是吗？
lt's quite a predicament here isn't it, Sid?
卡顿
Cotton
她说得很有理
l mean she makes a good point
我会考虑，也许你也该考虑
Let me think about this. Maybe you should too. l will bet you that・ ・ ・
我敢说黛安索而访问 有希望了
Diane Sawyer interview is looking real good right about now
没问题
Consider it done
好险
That was intense
嘿，席妮
Hey, Sidney・ ・ ・
我绝不会做出伤害你的事
l want you to know that l would never ever do anything to hurt you
卡顿，枪给我
Cotton, give me the gun
好，当然，拿去
Yeah. Okay. Sure. Take it
我们或许应该谈谈事发经过
Sidney, we should probably talk about what exactly happened here Get our stories straight?
谁来拉我上去
Can somebody get me out of here
盖儿，你还好吧？
Gale. Are you alright?
我中枪了，当然不好
l've been shot, of course not
手给我
Give me your hand, Gale
天哪，你吓死我了
Jesus Gale, you scared the crap out of me
下面没人了吧
There isn't anybody else down there is there?
没有
No
在跌落舞台报导到此为止
So much for reporting from the trenches, huh?
闭嘴
Shut up, Cotton
严不严重？
How bad is it?
子弹从我的肋骨弹开了
Bounced off my rib
天哪，你的命比猫还长
Jees, Gale you have more lives than a cat
给我一把枪
Give me one of those?
她死了吗？
ls she dead?
不知道，他们常会复活
l don't know. They always come back
以防万一
Just in case
差不多了，警长
That about wraps it up, Chief
好
Okay, Frank
轻点，断了几根肋骨
Take it easy, you've got a couple broken ribs there
盖儿，你没事吧
Gale. You alright?
乔
Joel?
我回来了
l'm back
我想我们或许能抢个独家
l was thinking maybe we could get the scoop like in the old days
魏盖儿在温莎大学报导
You're Gale Weathers at Windsor College
这边有个人还活着
We have a live one here
杜威
Dewey
我不敢相信你活着
l can't believe you are alive
没事吧
Are you okay?
盖儿
Gale
你撑着点
You hang in there
我跟你去
l'm coming with you
告诉我们你看到什么
Can you tell us what you saw?
里面发生了什么事
Can you tell us what happened in there?
席妮，请谈谈当英雄的感受
Sidney, can you tell us how it feels to be a hero?
他才是英雄，卡顿
Talk to Cotton
他才是采访对象，他是英雄
He's the man you want to interview He's the hero
发生什么事？ 为何你是英雄
What happened in there? Why are you a hero?
请说细节
Details, please
没人比我更想提供这个故事
Look guys, no one wants to give you this story more than l do
可惜要看时间地点和价码
Unfortunately, there's time and a place. lndeed a price for everything
随时打给我
So feel free to call me
卡顿，说一点嘛
Come on, Cotton Tell us something
至少有一件事我可以说
l'll tell you one thing
这故事会拍成很棒的电影 谢谢
lt'll make a hell of a movie Thank you
-=顶好精品论坛=-
BMDruCHinYaN荣誉出品
一贯秉持：小体积，高画质
www.bmdruchinyan.com
-=顶好精品论坛=-
BMDruCHinYaN荣誉出品
一贯秉持：小体积，高画质
www.bmdruchinyan.com